<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content"><channel><title>Luis Ascorbe</title><description>Software Developer. Tech Lead. Speaker. Conference Organizer.</description><link>https://lascorbe.com</link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 10:03:47 +0200</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 10:03:47 +0200</pubDate><ttl>250</ttl><atom:link href="https://lascorbe.com/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://lascorbe.com/posts/2020-04-21-hello-world</guid><title>Hello world!</title><description>Hi there from the trenches! 👋</description><link>https://lascorbe.com/posts/2020-04-21-hello-world</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 13:00:00 +0200</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hi there!</p><p>Welcome to my new blog. Thank you for wasting your time reading me, I mean, I'm pretty sure there's a new Netflix documentary that you haven't seen way more interesting than reading what an average human being from Spain could write. So thank you for reading 😊.<br><br>Why I made this? This is my 3rd or 4th attempt at trying to start a blog. I hope to be more consistent and write often. The good thing is that this is the first time I make a blog by myself, on my domain (years ago I used Blogger and Medium). So let's see how this goes 😃.</p><p>What about the content? I'm not completely sure if this is going to be a purely technical blog or I'm going to write about other things, I'll figure it out while driving. Anyway, for now, the topics will be mostly technical, I'm exploring SwiftUI so I think that's what I'm going to start with.</p><p>What about how I made this website? I made it entirely with <a href="https://github.com/JohnSundell/Publish">Publish</a>, a great tool to make websites with Swift, by my buddy <a href="https://twitter.com/JohnSundell">John Sundell</a>. Check it out, it's modular and versatile, John did an amazing job building it.</p><p>If you want to know how to make your website with <a href="https://github.com/JohnSundell/Publish">Publish</a>, 2 articles helped me to get started:</p><ul><li><a href="https://blog.bitomule.com/posts/getting-started-with-publish/">Getting started with publish</a> by my friend <a href="https://twitter.com/Bitomule">David Collado</a>.</li><li><a href="https://www.staskus.io/posts/2020-01-26-publish/">Migrating from Jekyll to Publish: A site generator for Swift developers</a> by <a href="https://twitter.com/PovilasStaskus">Povilas Staskus</a>.</li></ul><p>If you've reached this point chances are that you've completed Netflix and you do not have anything else to do, so here's a recommendation: go watch <a href="https://documentaryheaven.com/objectified/">Objectified</a> if you haven't yet. A great documentary on design and our relationships with products. Or you can always go to the <a href="https://vimeo.com/nsspain">NSSpain Vimeo channel</a> and watch a talk 😇.</p><p>Cheers ✌️.</p>]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>